# Thomaz Guadagnini Ramalheira

+55 19 994694064 thomaz@vivaldi.net linkedin.com/in/ThomazGR Campinas, São Paulo, Brazil

Finished studying Sports Science in June 2019. I have worked as an Undergraduate Researcher from 2017 until June 2019 and now I am a Master's degree student in studying nutrition and metabolism sciences. Skills include analytical thinking, problem solving and good communication acquired through 2+ years working in a scientific and laboratory environment.

### **Professional Experience**

AUGUST 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020

### Community XP & Support Analyst Gamers Club

-Customer service, ticket and chat support through Zendesk.

JULY 2017 - JULY 2019

## Undergraduate Student UNICAMP

- -DNA, RNA and miRNA extraction and expression;
- -Real-Time/q PCR;
- -SDS-PAGE/Gel electrophoresis and Western Blot;
- -Mouse handling and small surgery;
- -Cryosectioning and Oil Red staining tissues;
- -Entry-level experience in cell culture;
- -Statistical analysis utilizing GraphPad Prism;
- -Producing reports and results related to 2 finished scientific researches.

### Languages

- Portuguese Fluent/Native 10/10
- English Advanced level 9/10

#### Skills

- Major research laboratory experience;
- Focused in epigenetics, metabolic disorders, metabolic programming and bioinformatics.

#### **Education**

JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

### Master of Science, Nutrition and Metabolism

#### **UNICAMP**

- -Bioinformatic analysis: Gene Expression Omnibus (GEO), GEO2R, limma, KEGG, GO, MirDIP, miRBase, miRWalk and TargetScan;
- -Script development in Python and Pandas related to microRNA sequences, target genes finding and microarray analysis.

**JULY 2019** 

# **Bachelor's in Sports Science UNICAMP**

-Finished 2 researches focused on microRNA, metabolic disorders and metabolic programming. Both researches were funded by CNPq.